ANTOINE BINNER

HARDWARE TESTER

CONTACT

- +33 7 69 54 05 69
- Talence, France

PROFILE SUMMARY

Curious and desire to learn, I am a second-year student in Electrical Engineering & Industrial Computing. I am seeking a 3-year apprenticeship in the electronic engineering industry as a hardware tester. My career goal is to become an R&D engineer in microelectronics.

EDUCATION

2023 - PRESENT IUT BORDEAUX

 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering & Industrial Computing

2021 - 2023 SAINT-ANDRE HIGHSHCOOL COLMAR

High school diploma with honors

INTERESTS

- Sport
- · Computer science
- Travel
- Neurology

LANGUAGES

- French: Fluent
- English: Intermediate

PORTFOLIO

• antoinebinnera.wixsite.com/



WORK EXPERIENCE

Lolapalooza Festival

JULY 2023

Beverage seller

- Sold drinks to customers in both English and French while working in a team
- Gained experience in teamwork, following instructions and communicating with customers.

CURRICULAR ELECTRONICS PROJECTS

Kart with remote control

JANUARY 2024 - JUNE 2024

Design acquisition and action part

- In charge of designing sensors and motors of the kart
- Learnt more about working with a team, designing optical sensors and programming a microcontroller.

Bath thermometer

OCTOBER 2023 - JANUARY 2024

Design acquisition and power supply part

- In charge of designing sensors and the power supply of the electronic board
- Gained skills in presenting project rationale to an audience, writing technical documentation and soldering components.

SKILLS

- Curious
- Electronic signal processing
- Self-contained
- Proteus ISIS & ARES
- Discipline
- Visual Studio
- Attention to detail
- Programming languages : C, C#, Python